<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- TODO Make sure these match the values in the repo -->
<!-- TODO Make sure database rewrites to accommodate changes -->
<resources>
    <string name="definition_0_acceptance">A disposition to tolerate or accept people or situations.</string>
    <string name="definition_1_accomplishment">Having successfully achieved many things, especially after great difficulty</string>
    <string name="definition_2_accountability">An obligation or willingness to accept responsibility or to account for one\'s actions.</string>
    <string name="definition_3_accuracy">The quality or state of being correct or precise.</string>
    <string name="definition_4_achievement">The accomplishment of an aim or purpose.</string>
    <string name="definition_5_adaptability">The ability to adjust to new conditions.</string>
    <string name="definition_6_alertness">The quality or state of being alert and watchful.</string>
    <string name="definition_7_altruism">Selfless concern for the welfare of others.</string>
    <string name="definition_8_ambition">A strong desire to do or to achieve something, typically requiring determination and hard work.</string>
    <string name="definition_9_amusement">A feeling of great pleasure and enjoyment.</string>
    <string name="definition_10_assertiveness">the quality of being self-assured and confident without being aggressive.</string>
    <string name="definition_11_attentiveness">Paying careful attention to something or someone.</string>
    <string name="definition_12_awareness">The state or condition of being aware and noticing things around you.</string>
    <string name="definition_13_balance">Maintaining equilibrium in all aspects of one\'s life, avoiding extremes and finding a healthy middle ground.</string>
    <string name="definition_14_beauty">The quality present in a thing or person that gives intense pleasure or deep satisfaction to the mind, whether arising from sensory manifestations (as shape, color, sound, etc.), a meaningful design or pattern, or something else (as a personality in which high spiritual qualities are manifest).</string>
    <string name="definition_15_boldness">The quality of being brave and daring.</string> //Boldness and bravery synonyms?
    <string name="definition_16_bravery">The quality of mind or spirit that enables a person to face danger or pain without showing fear.</string>
    <string name="definition_17_brilliance">The quality of being intellectually very able.</string>
    <string name="definition_18_calm">A state of peace and quiet.</string>
    <string name="definition_19_candor">The quality of being open and honest in expression; frankness.</string>
    <string name="definition_20_capability">Having the ability, skill, or knowledge to do something.</string>
    <string name="definition_21_carefulness">The quality of being avoiding dang.</string>
    <string name="definition_22_certainty">The state of being certain.</string>
    <string name="definition_23_challenge">A call to take part in some contest, dispute, or competition.</string>
    <string name="definition_24_charity">The voluntary giving of help, typically in the form of money, to those in need.</string>
    <string name="definition_25_clarity">Free from doubt or ambiguity; unequivocal.</string>
    <string name="definition_26_cleanliness">The state of being clean.</string>
    <string name="definition_27_clever">Having or showing quickness and inventiveness in adapting to new situations.</string>
    <string name="definition_28_comfort">A state of physical ease and freedom from pain or constraint.</string>
    <string name="definition_29_commitment">The state or quality of being dedicated to a cause, activity, etc.</string>
    <string name="definition_30_common_sense">Sound and prudent judgment based on a simple perception of the situation or facts.</string>
    <string name="definition_31_communication">The imparting or exchanging of information by speaking, writing, or using some other medium.</string>
    <string name="definition_32_community">A group of people living in the same place or having a particular characteristic in common.</string>
    <string name="definition_33_compassion">The ability to show kindness and understanding towards others, even in difficult situations.</string>
    <string name="definition_34_competence">The quality of being adequately or well qualified for some task.</string>
    <string name="definition_35_concentration">The action or power of focusing one\'s mind on something.</string>
    <string name="definition_36_confidence">The feeling or belief that one can rely on someone or something; firm trust.</string>
    <string name="definition_37_connection">The state of being connected.</string>
    <string name="definition_38_consciousness">The state of being awake and aware of one\'s surroundings.</string>
    <string name="definition_39_consistency">The quality of being constant; regularity.</string>
    <string name="definition_40_contentment">A state of happiness and satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="definition_41_contribution">The action of giving or doing something to help a cause, person, or organization.</string>
    <string name="definition_42_control">The power to influence or direct people\'s behavior or the course of events.</string>
    <string name="definition_43_conviction">A firmly held belief or opinion.</string>
    <string name="definition_44_cooperation">The process of working together to the same end.</string>
    <string name="definition_45_courage">The ability to do something that frightens one.</string>
    <string name="definition_46_courtesy">Politeness, especially with regard to social conventions or rules.</string>
    <string name="definition_47_creativity">The use of imagination or original ideas to create something; inventiveness.</string>
    <string name="definition_48_credibility">The quality of being trusted and believed in.</string>
    <string name="definition_49_curiosity">A strong desire to know or learn something.</string>
    <string name="definition_50_decisiveness">The quality of being determined to do something.</string>
    <string name="definition_51_dedication">The quality of being dedicated to a task or purpose.</string>
    <string name="definition_52_dependability">The quality of being reliable, trustworthy, and consistent in one\'s actions and behaviors, often involving a sense of responsibility, accountability, and commitment.</string>
    <string name="definition_53_determination">The quality of being decided or resolved; firmness of purpose.</string>
    <string name="definition_54_development">The process of developing or being developed.</string>
    <string name="definition_55_devotion">Dedication and loyalty towards a cause, belief, or person, often demonstrated through consistent effort and sacrifice.</string>
    <string name="definition_56_dignity">A sense of self-respect and worthiness that allows one to carry oneself with honor and grace, regardless of circumstances or treatment by others.</string>
    <string name="definition_57_discipline">The practice of self-control and restraint, often in pursuit of a goal or ideal, that involves adhering to rules and routines even in the face of temptation or distraction.</string>
    <string name="definition_58_discovery">The action or process of discovering something.</string>
    <string name="definition_59_dreams">Aspirations and goals that are deeply personal and meaningful, often tied to a person\'s values, passions, and sense of purpose.</string>
    <string name="definition_60_drive">A strong inner motivation and determination to pursue one\'s goals and aspirations, often characterized by enthusiasm, focus, and persistence.</string>
    <string name="definition_61_duty">A moral or legal obligation; responsibility.</string>
    <string name="definition_62_earnestness">The quality of being serious and sincere.</string>
    <string name="definition_63_effectiveness">The quality of being successful in producing a desired or intended result.</string>
    <string name="definition_64_efficiency">The state or quality of being efficient.</string>
    <string name="definition_65_elegance">The quality of being pleasingly graceful and stylish in appearance or manner.</string>
    <string name="definition_66_empathy">The ability to understand and share the feelings of another.</string>
    <string name="definition_67_endurance">The fact or power of enduring an unpleasant or difficult process or situation without giving way.</string>
    <string name="definition_68_energy">The strength and vitality required for sustained physical or mental activity.</string>
    <string name="definition_69_enjoyment">The state or process of taking pleasure in something.</string>
    <string name="definition_70_enthusiasm">A feeling of intense and eager enjoyment, interest, or approval.</string>
    <string name="definition_71_equity">The quality of being fair and impartial.</string>
    <string name="definition_72_ethics">Moral principles that govern a person\'s behavior or the conducting of an activity.</string>
    <string name="definition_73_excellence">The quality of being outstanding or extremely good.</string>
    <string name="definition_74_excitement">A feeling of great enthusiasm and eagerness.</string>
    <string name="definition_75_experience">Practical contact with and observation of facts or events.</string>
    <string name="definition_76_exercise">Physical activity, especially that done to maintain or improve health and fitness.</string>
    <string name="definition_77_exploration">The action of traveling in or through an unfamiliar area in order to learn about it.</string>
    <string name="definition_78_expressiveness">The quality of effectively conveying thought or feeling.</string>
    <string name="definition_79_faith">Complete trust or confidence in someone or something.</string>
    <string name="definition_80_fairness">The quality of being just, impartial, and honest.</string>
    <string name="definition_81_fame">The state or condition of being known or talked about by many people.</string>
    <string name="definition_82_favors">Inclination toward giving a kind action or gesture.</string>
    <string name="definition_83_fearlessness">The quality of being brave.</string>
    <string name="definition_84_feelings">An emotional state or reaction.</string>
    <string name="definition_85_ferocity">The state or quality of being ferocious.</string>
    <string name="definition_86_fidelity">Faithfulness to a person, cause, or belief, demonstrated by continuing loyalty and support.</string>
    <string name="definition_87_flexibility">The ability to adapt and adjust to changing circumstances, perspectives, and expectations, without compromising one\'s values or goals.</string>
    <string name="definition_88_focus">The ability to concentrate one\'s attention and efforts on a specific task or objective, often involving filtering out distractions and maintaining a clear sense of purpose.</string>
    <string name="definition_89_foresight">The ability to predict or the action of predicting what will happen or be needed in the future.</string>
    <string name="definition_90_forgiveness">The act of letting go of resentment or anger towards someone who has wronged you, often characterized by empathy, understanding, and a desire to move on.</string>
    <string name="definition_91_fortitude">Courage in pain or adversity.</string>
    <string name="definition_92_freedom">The power or right to act, speak, or think as one wants without hindrance or restraint.</string>
    <string name="definition_93_friendship">A deep and meaningful connection between two or more people that is characterized by mutual affection, trust, support, and respect.</string>
    <string name="definition_94_generosity">The quality of being kind and generous.</string>
    <string name="definition_95_genius">Exceptional intellectual or creative power or other natural ability.</string>
    <string name="definition_96_giving">The act of bestowing as a gift; a conferring or imparting.</string>
    <string name="definition_97_goodness">A moral and ethical quality that involves doing what is right, just, and fair, often in the service of others.</string>
    <string name="definition_98_grace">Simple elegance or refinement of movement.</string>
    <string name="definition_99_gratitude">The quality of being thankful; readiness to show appreciation for and to return kindness.</string>
    <string name="definition_100_greatness">The quality of being great, distinguished, or eminent.</string>
    <string name="definition_101_growth">The process of learning and improving oneself.</string>
    <string name="definition_102_guidance">The provision of direction, advice, and support to help someone achieve their goals, often through mentorship, coaching, or counseling.</string>
    <string name="definition_103_happiness">A state of positive emotion and well-being that is characterized by contentment, pleasure, and satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="definition_104_hard_work">Putting in great deal of effort or endurance.</string>
    <string name="definition_105_harmony">The quality of forming a pleasing and consistent whole.</string>
    <string name="definition_106_health">The state of being free from illness or injury.</string>
    <string name="definition_107_helping_friends">The act of assisting people close to you.</string>
    <string name="definition_108_helping_strangers">The act of assisting people you don\'t know.</string>
    <string name="definition_109_honesty">The quality of telling the truth whenever possible.</string>
    <string name="definition_110_honor">High respect; esteem.</string>
    <string name="definition_111_hope">A feeling of expectation and desire for a certain thing to happen.</string>
    <string name="definition_112_hospitality">The friendly and generous reception and entertainment of guests, visitors, or strangers.</string>
    <string name="definition_113_humility">A modest view of one\'s own importance; humbleness.</string>
    <string name="definition_114_imagination">The faculty or action of forming new ideas, or images or concepts of external objects not present to the senses.</string>
    <string name="definition_115_improvement">The process of making something, especially oneself better.</string>
    <string name="definition_116_independence">The ability to think, act, and make decisions without being overly influenced by others, often involving self-reliance, autonomy, and freedom.</string>
    <string name="definition_117_individuality">The quality or character of a particular person that distinguishes them from others of the same kind, especially when strongly marked.</string>
    <string name="definition_118_industriousness">Diligence; hard-working.</string>
    <string name="definition_119_influence">The capacity to have an effect on the character, development, or behavior of someone or something, or the effect itself.</string>
    <string name="definition_120_innovation">The process of creating something new or original that brings value or solves a problem, often involving creativity, experimentation, and risk-taking.</string>
    <string name="definition_121_inquisitiveness">An eager desire to know or learn something.</string>
    <string name="definition_122_insight">The quality of having an accurate and deep understanding.</string>
    <string name="definition_123_inspiration">The process of being mentally stimulated to do or feel something, especially to do something creative.</string>
    <string name="definition_124_integrity">The quality of being honest and having strong moral principles.</string>
    <string name="definition_125_intelligence">The ability to acquire and apply knowledge and skills.</string>
    <string name="definition_126_intensity">The quality of being passionate, focused, and committed to a task or objective, often involving a high level of energy and effort.</string>
    <string name="definition_127_intimacy">Close familiarity or friendship.</string>
    <string name="definition_128_intuition">The ability to understand something immediately, without the need for conscious reasoning.</string>
    <string name="definition_129_inventiveness">The quality of being inventive; creativity.</string>
    <string name="definition_130_joy">A feeling of great pleasure and happiness.</string>
    <string name="definition_131_justice">Just behavior or treatment.</string>
    <string name="definition_132_kindness">The quality of being friendly, generous, and considerate.</string>
    <string name="definition_133_knowledge">Facts, information, and skills acquired by a person through experience or education; the theoretical or practical understanding of a subject.</string>
    <string name="definition_134_lawfulness">Conformity to, or permitted by law or rules.</string>
    <string name="definition_135_leadership">The action of leading a group of people or an organization.</string>
    <string name="definition_136_learning">The acquisition of knowledge or skills through experience, study, or by being taught.</string>
    <string name="definition_137_liberty">The state of being free within society from oppressive restrictions imposed by authority on one\'s way of life, behavior, or political views.</string>
    <string name="definition_138_logic">Reasoning conducted or assessed according to strict principles of validity.</string>
    <string name="definition_139_love">An intense feeling of deep affection.</string>
    <string name="definition_140_loyalty">The quality of being loyal to someone or something.</string>
    <string name="definition_141_mastery">Comprehensive knowledge or skill in a subject or accomplishment.</string>
    <string name="definition_142_maturity">The state, fact, or period of being mature.</string>
    <string name="definition_143_meaning">The significance or purpose that something holds, often tied to a person\'s values, beliefs, and sense of identity.</string>
    <string name="definition_144_moderation">The avoidance of excess or extremes, especially in one\'s behavior or political opinions.</string>
    <string name="definition_145_motivation">The reason or reasons one has for acting or behaving in a particular way.</string>
    <string name="definition_146_openness">The quality of being open to new ideas and opinions.</string>
    <string name="definition_147_optimism">Hopefulness and confidence about the future or the successful outcome of something.</string>
    <string name="definition_148_order">The arrangement or disposition of people or things in relation to each other according to a particular sequence, pattern, or method.</string>
    <string name="definition_149_organization">An organized body of people with a particular purpose, especially a business, society, association, etc.</string>
    <string name="definition_150_originality">The ability to think independently and creatively.</string>
    <string name="definition_151_passion">Strong and barely controllable emotion.</string>
    <string name="definition_152_patience">The capacity to accept or tolerate delay, trouble, or suffering without getting angry or upset.</string>
    <string name="definition_153_peace">Freedom from disturbance; tranquility.</string>
    <string name="definition_154_performance">The level of achievement or success that is demonstrated in a particular task or domain, often involving skills, abilities, and effort.</string>
    <string name="definition_155_persistence">Firm or obstinate continuance in a course of action in spite of difficulty or opposition.</string>
    <string name="definition_156_playfulness">Full of fun and high spirits.</string>
    <string name="definition_157_poise">Graceful and elegant bearing in a person.</string>
    <string name="definition_158_potential">Having or showing the capacity to become or develop into something in the future.</string>
    <string name="definition_159_power">The ability to influence or control others or a situation, often involving resources, status, or authority.</string>
    <string name="definition_160_presence">The quality of being fully engaged and attentive in the present moment, often involving mindfulness, awareness, and openness.</string>
    <string name="definition_161_productivity">The level of efficiency and effectiveness in completing tasks or achieving goals, often involving time management, organization, and focus.</string>
    <string name="definition_162_professionalism">The adherence to ethical standards, norms, and behaviors that are expected in a particular profession or field, often involving competence, reliability, and integrity.</string>
    <string name="definition_163_prosperity">The state of being successful, wealthy, and flourishing, often involving financial abundance, health, and happiness.</string>
    <string name="definition_164_punctuality">The fact or quality of being on time.</string>
    <string name="definition_165_purpose">A clear and meaningful reason for existing or pursuing a particular goal, often tied to one\'s values, passions, and sense of fulfillment.</string>
    <string name="definition_166_rationality">The quality of being based on or in accordance with reason or logic.</string>
    <string name="definition_167_realism">The attitude or practice of accepting a situation as it is and being prepared to deal with it accordingly.</string>
    <string name="definition_168_reason">A cause, explanation, or justification for an action or event.</string>
    <string name="definition_169_recognition">Identification of someone or something or person from previous encounters or knowledge.</string>
    <string name="definition_170_recreation">Activity done for enjoyment when one is not working.</string>
    <string name="definition_171_refinement">The process of removing impurities or unwanted elements from a substance.</string>
    <string name="definition_172_reflection">The throwing back by a body or surface of light, heat, or sound without absorbing it.</string>
    <string name="definition_173_reliability">The quality of being trustworthy or of performing consistently well.</string>
    <string name="definition_174_resilience">The capacity to recover quickly from difficulties; toughness.</string>
    <string name="definition_175_resolution">A firm decision to do or not to do something.</string>
    <string name="definition_176_resourcefulness">The ability to find quick and clever ways to overcome difficulties.</string>
    <string name="definition_177_respect">A feeling of deep admiration for someone or something elicited by their abilities, qualities, or achievements.</string>
    <string name="definition_178_responsibility">The state or fact of having a duty to deal with something or of having control over someone.</string>
    <string name="definition_179_responsiveness">The quality of reacting quickly and positively.</string>
    <string name="definition_180_rest">An instance or period of relaxing or ceasing to engage in strenuous or stressful activity.</string>
    <string name="definition_181_restraint">The act of exercising self-control and moderation, often to avoid excess or inappropriate behavior or emotion.</string>
    <string name="definition_182_reverence">Deep respect for someone or something.</string>
    <string name="definition_183_rigor">The quality of being extremely thorough, exhaustive, or accurate.</string>
    <string name="definition_184_risk_taking">Willingness or enthusiasm for entering situation involving exposure to danger.</string>
    <string name="definition_185_satisfaction">A sense of contentment and fulfillment that comes from achieving a goal or fulfilling a desire, often accompanied by a feeling of pleasure or gratification.</string>
    <string name="definition_186_security">The state of being free from danger or threat.</string>
    <string name="definition_187_self_reliance">Depending on one\'s own powers and resources rather than those of others.</string>
    <string name="definition_188_self_awareness">Conscious knowledge of one\'s own character, feelings, motives, and desires.</string>
    <string name="definition_189_self_control">The ability to control oneself, in particular one\'s emotions and desires or the expression of them in one\'s behavior, especially in difficult situations.</string>
    <string name="definition_190_selflessness">Concern more with the needs and wishes of others than with one\'s own.</string>
    <string name="definition_191_sensitivity">The ability to perceive and respond to the feelings and needs of oneself and others, often characterized by empathy, compassion, and understanding.</string>
    <string name="definition_192_serenity">The state of being calm, peaceful, and untroubled.</string>
    <string name="definition_193_service">The action of helping or doing work for someone.</string>
    <string name="definition_194_sharing">The use of a resource or space by different individuals or the elements of a group.</string>
    <string name="definition_195_silence">Absence of sound.</string>
    <string name="definition_196_simplicity">The quality or condition of being plain or natural.</string>
    <string name="definition_197_sincerity">The quality of being free from pretense, deceit, or hypocrisy.</string>
    <string name="definition_198_skillfulness">The ability to do something well; expertise.</string>
    <string name="definition_199_solitude">The state or situation of being alone.</string>
    <string name="definition_200_spirituality">Belief in mysterious or supernatural connections or forces</string>
    <string name="definition_201_spontaneity">The condition of being spontaneous; spontaneous behavior or action.</string>
    <string name="definition_202_stability">The state of being stable.</string>
    <string name="definition_203_status">The relative social, professional, or other standing of someone or something.</string>
    <string name="definition_204_stewardship">The job of supervising or taking care of something, such as an organization or property.</string>
    <string name="definition_205_strength">The quality or state of being physically, mentally, or emotionally strong.</string>
    <string name="definition_206_structure">The arrangement of and relations between the parts or elements of something complex.</string>
    <string name="definition_207_success">The accomplishment of an aim or purpose.</string>
    <string name="definition_208_support">Bear all or part of the weight of; hold up.</string>
    <string name="definition_209_surprise">An unexpected or astonishing event, fact, or thing.</string>
    <string name="definition_210_sustainability">The ability to be maintained at a certain rate or level.</string>
    <string name="definition_211_sympathy">Feelings of pity and sorrow for someone else\'s misfortune.  Especially misfortune one hasn't personally experienced</string>
    <string name="definition_212_talent">Natural aptitude or skill.</string>
    <string name="definition_213_teamwork">The combined action of a group of people, especially when effective and efficient.</string>
    <string name="definition_214_temperance">Moderation in action, thought, or feeling : restraint. : habitual moderation in the indulgence of the appetites or passions</string>
    <string name="definition_215_thankfulness">Aware and appreciative of a benefit; grateful.</string>
    <string name="definition_216_thoroughness">The quality of being thorough.</string>
    <string name="definition_217_thoughtfulness">Showing consideration for the needs of other people.</string>
    <string name="definition_218_thrift">The quality of using money and other resources carefully and not wastefully.</string>
    <string name="definition_219_timelessness">Not affected by the passage of time or changes in fashion.</string>
    <string name="definition_220_tolerance">The ability to accept and respect the beliefs, opinions, and behaviors of others, even if they differ from one\'s own, often involving a commitment to fairness, open-mindedness, and non-judgmental attitudes.</string>
    <string name="definition_221_toughness">The quality of being strong enough to withstand adverse conditions or rough or careless handling.</string>
    <string name="definition_222_tradition">The transmission of customs or beliefs from generation to generation, or the fact of being passed on in this way.</string>
    <string name="definition_223_tranquility">A state of calmness, peacefulness, and serenity, often achieved through relaxation, meditation, or other forms of stress reduction.</string>
    <string name="definition_224_transparency">The quality of being open, honest, and clear in one\'s communication and actions, often involving sharing information and being accountable for one\'s decisions.</string>
    <string name="definition_225_trust">Firm belief in the reliability, truth, ability, or strength of someone or something.</string>
    <string name="definition_226_trustworthiness">The ability to be relied on as honest or truthful.</string>
    <string name="definition_227_truth">The quality of being in accordance with fact, reality, or sincerity, often involving honesty, accuracy, and authenticity.</string>
    <string name="definition_228_understanding">The ability to comprehend or grasp the nature, significance, or meaning of something, often involving empathy, insight, and knowledge.</string>
    <string name="definition_229_uniqueness">The quality of being the only one of its kind.</string>
    <string name="definition_230_unity">The state of being united, joined, or connected, often involving a shared purpose, goal, or identity.</string>
    <string name="definition_231_valor">Great courage in the face of danger, especially in battle.</string>
    <string name="definition_232_victory">An act of defeating an enemy or opponent in a battle, game, or other competition.</string>
    <string name="definition_233_vigor">Physical strength and good health.</string>
    <string name="definition_234_vision">The faculty or state of being able to see.</string>
    <string name="definition_235_vitality">The state of being strong and active; energy.</string>
    <string name="definition_236_wealth">An abundance of valuable possessions or money.</string>
    <string name="definition_237_welcoming"> The act of making someone feel accepted, valued, and comfortable in a particular setting or community, often involving hospitality, kindness, and inclusiveness.</string>
    <string name="definition_238_wholeness">The state of forming a complete and harmonious whole; unity.</string>
    <string name="definition_239_wisdom">The quality of having experience, knowledge, and good judgment; the quality of being wise.</string>
    <string name="definition_240_wonder">A feeling of surprise mingled with admiration, caused by something beautiful, unexpected, unfamiliar, or inexplicable.</string>
    <string name="definition_241_worthiness">The quality of being good enough, suitable, or the right thing to do.</string>
    <string name="definition_242_zeal">Great energy or enthusiasm in pursuit of a cause or an objective.</string>
</resources>